[
     {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 45? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "6358.5",
      "options": [
        "6360.0",
        "6361.5",
        "6358.5",
        "6357.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 19? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "1133.54",
      "options": [
        "1136.54",
        "1133.54",
        "1135.04",
        "1132.04"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 4? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "50.24",
      "options": [
        "51.74",
        "50.24",
        "53.24",
        "48.74"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 20? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "1256.0",
      "options": [
        "1259.0",
        "1256.0",
        "1254.5",
        "1257.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 36? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "4069.44",
      "options": [
        "4069.44",
        "4070.94",
        "4067.94",
        "4072.44"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 67? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "14095.46",
      "options": [
        "14093.96",
        "14095.46",
        "14096.96",
        "14098.46"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 46? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "6644.24",
      "options": [
        "6647.24",
        "6644.24",
        "6642.74",
        "6645.74"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 61? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "11683.94",
      "options": [
        "11682.44",
        "11685.44",
        "11686.94",
        "11683.94"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 26? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "2122.64",
      "options": [
        "2125.64",
        "2122.64",
        "2124.14",
        "2121.14"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 34? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "3629.84",
      "options": [
        "3632.84",
        "3628.34",
        "3629.84",
        "3631.34"
      ]
    }
]